Finding Aid for the Bob Brown Papers LSC.0723
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Gastronomy--Manuscript, Cheeses of All Nations (lit. references & popular sayings). (Box 84)
- Gastronomy--Notes and Drafts. (Box 84)
- Gastronomy--Notes, Clippings for Cheeses of All Nations. (Box 84)
- Gastronomy--Notes, Clippings, Drafts for Cheeses of All Nations. (Box 84)
- Gastronomy--Recipes. (Box 84)
- Manuscript -- Beer Gardening. (Box 84)
- Manuscript -- City Fishing. (Box 84)
- Manuscript--"Starving" Russia, by Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 84)
- Manuscript--Crachez un Peu!, by Bob Brown. (Box 84)
- Manuscript--Good-Bye Mr. Brown, How Are You. (Box 84)
- Manuscript--In Darkest Harlem, Negro Hell, by Bob Brown. (Box 84)
- Manuscript--It Tastes Like Chicken, by Bob Brown. (Box 84)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 84)
- Note--Last Stanza of "Dover Beach", copied by hand. (Box 84)
- Notes--scrap paper. (Box 84)
- Pamphlet--Brazil at a Glance. (Box 84)
- Pamphlet--The Negro and American Literature, by E. Clay. (Box 84)
- Periodical--red pen. (Box 84)
- Poetry--It's Nice in Nice. (Box 84)
- Poetry--untitled draft. (Box 84)
- Publication--A Testimony by Robert Carlton Brown. (Box 84)
- Publication--CONTEMPO, a Bob Brown Issue. (Box 84)
- Publication--The Wet Wallpaper, by Robert Carlton Brown. (Box 84)
- Archaeological Records--Museo Paraense. (Box 85)
- Book Cover--Salads and Herbs, by Cora, Rose, and Bob Brown. (Box 85)
- Clippings. (Box 85)
- Clippings--Women's Day. (Box 85)
- Correspondence. (Box 85)
- Ephemera. (Box 85)
- Ephemera--Invitation to the Blindman's Ball. (Box 85)
- Gastronomy--Notes, Clippings on Soup. (Box 85)
- Gastronomy--Notes, Clippings, Recipes. (Box 85)
- Lease--Gray's Inn. (Box 85)
- Manuscript, Notes for "Negro Book". (Box 85)
- Manuscript--A Gentlemen's Country, by Bob Brown. (Box 85)
- Manuscript--A Nutting We Will Go!, by Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 85)
- Manuscript--Beer Soup and Pretzels, by Bob Brown. (Box 85)
- Manuscript--Bringing 'Em Back Alive, by Bob Brown. (Box 85)
- Manuscript--Carnival and the Feria, by Bob Brown. (Box 85)
- Manuscript--Cock-Fighting, by Bob Brown. (Box 85)
- Manuscript--Meet Me After the Rain (carbons). (Box 85)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 85)
- Manuscript--Watch Your Liquor-Fall, by Bob Brown. (Box 85)
- Notes/Scrap paper. (Box 85)
- Periodical--Direction. (Box 85)
- Periodical--Poster Love. (Box 85)
- Periodical--The Fly Leaf. (Box 85)
- Periodical--The Western College Magazine. (Box 85)
- Advertisement--Moscow Tour. (Box 86)
- Archaeological Newsletter. (Box 86)
- Brochure--Travel in Brazil (with 2 original photographs by the Browns inserted). (Box 86)
- Clippings. (Box 86)
- Clippings--National Geographic article on Columbian artifacts. (Box 86)
- Correspondence. (Box 86)
- Correspondence--Letter to Menken. (Box 86)
- Manuscript--El Jueves, by Bob Brown. (Box 86)
- Manuscript--Hoboing the Harvest, by John Walker Gunn. (Box 86)
- Manuscript--In Chilly Spain, by Bob Brown. (Box 86)
- Manuscript--Le Semana Santa, by Bob Brown. (Box 86)
- Manuscript--Lead, Kindly Guide, by Bob Brown. (Box 86)
- Manuscript--Los Toros, by Bob Brown. (Box 86)
- Manuscript--Lottery and Life, by Bob Brown. (Box 86)
- Manuscript--Mother Love, by Bob Brown. (Box 86)
- Manuscript--Noise, by Bob Brown. (Box 86)
- Manuscript--Romantic Spain, by Bob Brown. (Box 86)
- Manuscripts--incomplete. (Box 86)
- Manuscript--Spanish Gambling, by Bob Brown. (Box 86)
- Manuscript--The Joy of Giving, by Bob Brown. (Box 86)
- Manuscript--The Novadedes, by Bob Brown. (Box 86)
- Manuscript--Ther "Mer-Cow", by Bob Brown. (Box 86)
- Notes for "Nigger Story". (Box 86)
- Notes/Scrap paper. (Box 86)
- Cover Letter--for Let There Be Beer!. (Box 87)
- Cover Letter--Hollywood consulting re: Latin America. (Box 87)
- Ephemera. (Box 87)
- Ephemera--Jargon Press Newsletter. (Box 87)
- Estate--"Bob Brown Personal Collection" (biographical note & list of library contents by unknown party). (Box 87)
- Gastronomy--Clippings. (Box 87)
- Journal Entries--by Cora Brown re: Asia Trip. (Box 87)
- Kay Boyle--A Comeallye for Robert Carlton Brown. (Box 87)
- Manuscript--Advertising Fright. (Box 87)
- Manuscript--Bankers Behind Bars. (Box 87)
- Manuscript--Clams. (Box 87)
- Manuscript--Ed's One-Man Magazine. (Box 87)
- Manuscript--Real America. (Box 87)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 87)
- Manuscript--The Cartoon Liberty League. (Box 87)
- Manuscript--The Future of Radical Writing. (Box 87)
- Manuscript--The Land of Happy Children, Cornelia L.F. Brown. (Box 87)
- Manuscript--The Treasure Island Venture (70 pp.). (Box 87)
- Note--How to Have Fun With the Radio. (Box 87)
- Notes/Scrap Paper. (Box 87)
- Poetry--damaged drafts. (Box 87)
- Poetry--drafts. (Box 87)
- Poetry--Mathematics (Mathematics of Life in Paris). (Box 87)
- Poetry--My Margonary (table of contents). (Box 87)
- Poetry--untitled drafts. (Box 87)
- Poetry--untitled long poem. (Box 87)
- Rare and fine Book Catalogs. (Box 87)
- Advertisement--Moscow Tour. (Box 88)
- Bibliographical list--Cookbooks by Cora, Rose, and Bob Brown. (Box 88)
- Chapter Outline--The Amazon Flows On. (Box 88)
- Clippings. (Box 88)
- Clippings--Bob Brown Books (posthumous biographical info.). (Box 88)
- Clippings--Publisher's Bluff, by James Laughlin. (Box 88)
- Clippings--Review of Nomadness. (Box 88)
- Clippings--The New Yorker. (Box 88)
- Clippings--Visual Materials. (Box 88)
- Correspondence. (Box 88)
- Customer list--Eighth St. Bookshop. (Box 88)
- Draft--Autobiographical Material. (Box 88)
- Drafts--Return to Rio. (Box 88)
- Ephemera. (Box 88)
- Gastronomy--Table of Contents, Portuguese and Brazilian Cuisines. (Box 88)
- Geometrical Print--Hiler 1950. (Box 88)
- Manuscript, Notes--Going Places, Doing Things (autobiographical material). (Box 88)
- Manuscript, Notes--Painting the Orchid, by Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 88)
- Manuscript--Chapter 1, "You had better leave that ring in the vault..." (Box 88)
- Manuscript--Coffee: Two Buck a Pound, by Bob Brown. (Box 88)
- Manuscript--Dey Likes it Dat Way. (Box 88)
- Manuscript--Life's a Funny Place to Be. (Box 88)
- Manuscript--Moscow 1935, Day & Night. (Box 88)
- Manuscript--Moscow Tempo 1935. (Box 88)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 88)
- Manuscript--So This Is Moscow!. (Box 88)
- Manuscript--Stretching the Rubber Question. (Box 88)
- Manuscript--The Barnum of All Books. (Box 88)
- Manuscript--The coucho and jebe of the Amazons. (Box 88)
- Manuscript--The Streets of Moscow. (Box 88)
- Marketing Proposal for "Soul Kisses" candy, allegedly signed by Thomas Hardy. (Box 88)
- Note--Books and I Are Bound. (Box 88)
- Notes, Drafts--for Nomadness. (Box 88)
- Notes--Amazon Artifacts. (Box 88)
- Notes--on Bahia Dolls. (Box 88)
- Notes--Xray Stay. (Box 88)
- Periodical--Hobbies, The Magazine for the Collector. (Box 88)
- Periodical--Time Magazine. (Box 88)
- Photo Negative--"The Night at the Refuge" (short story). (Box 88)
- Poetry--"London". (Box 88)
- Poetry--Drafts and Typescripts for Demonics. (Box 88)
- Press Clippings--reviews of Amazing Amazon. (Box 88)
- Sketch. (Box 88)
- Sportfisherman's Identification Card, with photo. (Box 88)
- Voter Registration Slips, City of Los Angeles, Bob & Rose Brown. (Box 88)
- WPA Notice. (Box 88)
- Clippings. (Box 89)
- Clippings--Book Reviews. (Box 89)
- Correspondence. (Box 89)
- Drafts, Clippings, Correspondence--Biography of Santos Dumont. (Box 89)
- Ephemera. (Box 89)
- Gastronomy--Clippings. (Box 89)
- Gastronomy--Notes. (Box 89)
- Gastronomy--Notes for The Complete Book of Cheese. (Box 89)
- Gastronomy--Notes, Clippings for the The Complete Book of Cheese. (Box 89)
- Notes, synopses, Chapter 1 manuscript--Taja the Potter, by Rose Brown. (Box 89)
- Notes/Scrap Paper. (Box 89)
- Pamphlet--Jargon 39, by Jonathan Williams. (Box 89)
- Periodical--New Masses, "Edmund Wilson's Globe of Glass," by Joseph Freeman. (Box 89)
- Picture Captions--Playing Indian and Riding Herd for Hitler. (Box 89)
- Poetry--Drafts. (Box 89)
- Poetry--manuscript of "Sextettes," from Demonics. (Box 89)
- Poetry--manuscripts from My Marjonary. (Box 89)
- Portrait of Bob Brown, by Fielding Dawson. (Box 89)
- Preslit--Constructive Suggestions. (Box 89)
- U.S.S.R. Tourist Certificate. (Box 89)
- Autobiographical Statement for International Literature. (Box 90)
- Biographical Note re: family and marriages. (Box 90)
- Clippings. (Box 90)
- Commemorative statement by a friend, written shortly after Brown's death. (Box 90)
- Correspondence. (Box 90)
- Correspondence, Clippings, Petitions, Notes--action against Petropolis bone factory. (Box 90)
- Correspondence--Eleanor Parker Brown. (Box 90)
- Ephemera. (Box 90)
- Manuscript--I Taught in Hitch-hike College, by Bob Brown. (Box 90)
- Manuscript--Recipes from the Portugese, by Bob, Rose, and Cora Brown. (Box 90)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 90)
- Notes/Scrap Paper. (Box 90)
- Notes--The Dictionary of ALL Drinks, by Bob Brown. (Box 90)
- Publication--"Slacker's Hotel," by Bob Brown (in _The Left_). (Box 90)
- Biographical entry for "Who's Who in America". (Box 91)
- Clippings. (Box 91)
- Clippings--"The Negro and American Culture," by V.F. Calverton, That Saturday Review of Literature. (Box 91)
- Clippings--editorial announcement re: Robert Carlton Brown. (Box 91)
- Clippings--movie poster for "Crack-Up". (Box 91)
- Clippings--review of "The Selected Writings of Guillaume Apollinaire". (Box 91)
- Correspondence. (Box 91)
- Correspondence--"Steamer letter ot Robert Carlton Brown from his friends Joe and Muddy" (w photos). (Box 91)
- Correspondence--Kay Boyle. (Box 91)
- Correspondence--R.C. Brown to Bob & Rose re: his stay in mental hospital. (Box 91)
- Ephemera. (Box 91)
- Ephemera--tiny address book, from Kyoto. (Box 91)
- Epitaph for Brown by Walter Lowefels. (Box 91)
- Financial Report re: British American. (Box 91)
- Gastronomy--Clippings. (Box 91)
- Gastronomy--recipes. (Box 91)
- Gastronomy--Recipes and Notes. (Box 91)
- Manuscript, Notes--Corksrew Guide to Greenwich Village, by Bob Brown and Larry Gellert. (Box 92)
- Manuscript/notes--Buy British, by Bob Brown. (Box 92)
- Manuscript--Absolutely Bob Brown (allegedly an unpublished portrait by Gertude Stein). (Box 92)
- Manuscript--Brown Family Robinson, by Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 92)
- Manuscript--Estatutos de la Mexican American. (Box 92)
- Manuscript--Gastronomic Tour, by Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 92)
- Manuscript--Gorrillas in the Subway, by Bob Brown. (Box 92)
- Manuscript--Gran Circo Bufalo Bill, by Bob Brown. (Box 92)
- Manuscript--handwritten dramatic script. (Box 92)
- Manuscript--Homers (3 copies), by Bob Brown. (Box 92)
- Manuscript--Miami Invites You!, by Bob Brown. (Box 92)
- Manuscript--Middle Man's Profit, by Bob Brown. (Box 92)
- Manuscript--Our Day. (Box 92)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 92)
- Manuscript--Say it With Flowers, by Rose Brown. (Box 92)
- Manuscript--Synopsis of an article on Birds, by Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 92)
- Manuscript--The Barnum of all Books, by Bob Brown. (Box 92)
- Manuscript--The Lord Boys, by Bob Brown. (Box 92)
- Manuscript--The Scarlet Letters, by Bob Brown. (Box 92)
- Manuscript--The Three Magic Doses, by Bob Brown. (Box 92)
- Manuscript--The Wine of Life, by Bob Brown. (Box 92)
- Manuscript--What She Wanted, by Bob Brown. (Box 92)
- Manuscript--Whispering Water, by Bob Brown. (Box 92)
- Notebook. (Box 92)
- Note--Potential Expatriate. (Box 92)
- Notes/Scrap Paper. (Box 92)
- Notes--plots for stories. (Box 92)
- Obituary--Cora Brown. (Box 92)
- Obituary--Mrs. James Joyce. (Box 92)
- Periodical--The N.Z. Rationalist. (Box 92)
- Poetic "Portrait" of Brown by Carl Sandburg. (Box 92)
- Poetry--Lest We Forget: The Battle of Anacostia. (Box 92)
- Poetry--occasional piece for 73rd Birthday. (Box 92)
- Publication--"The American Writer's Plight," International Literature. (Box 92)
- Publication--Eating Upstairs, by Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 92)
- Publication--In at the Creation. (Box 92)
- Publication--pages from Globe-Gliding. (Box 92)
- Royalty Statements. (Box 92)
- Table of Contents--Fit for a King!, by Bob Brown. (Box 92)
- Wedding Invitation for marriage to Eleanor Wilson. (Box 92)
- Clippings. (Box 93)
- Clippings--re: Amazing Amazon. (Box 93)
- Correspondence. (Box 93)
- Correspondence--letters from Carlton Brown. (Box 93)
- Draft--"Special Subscription Offer" for a new journal. (Box 93)
- Ephemera. (Box 93)
- List--Books for Reprint. (Box 93)
- Manuscript--A Couple of Funerals, by Bob Brown. (Box 93)
- Manuscript--An Inky Day for Harry. (Box 93)
- Manuscript--Beer - A Gift of the Gods?. (Box 93)
- Manuscript--Beer Music. (Box 93)
- Manuscript--Beerland, by Bob Brown. (Box 93)
- Manuscript--Blood and Beer. (Box 93)
- Manuscript--Congress Signs Off for the Summer, by Bob Brown. (Box 93)
- Manuscript--For Cat's Sake!. (Box 93)
- Manuscript--How to Drink Beer. (Box 93)
- Manuscript--How to Ride Your Hobby. (Box 93)
- Manuscript--In the Devil's Dell, by Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 93)
- Manuscript--Jiu Jitsu in Five Easy Lessons, by Carlton Brown. (Box 93)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 93)
- Manuscript--Shoot If You Must. (Box 93)
- Manuscript--The Game of Chachango. (Box 93)
- Manuscript--The Horse Butcher, by Rose Brown. (Box 93)
- Manuscript--Those Good Old Days Brought Back Again. (Box 93)
- Notes/Outline--Brazil, by Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 93)
- Notes/Scrap Paper. (Box 93)
- Notes--Errors of Fact in "Mighty River of Brazil". (Box 93)
- Notes--Medical History. (Box 93)
- Notes--on Santos Dumont. (Box 93)
- Poetry--Noise Game. (Box 93)
- Prospectus--The Amazon Flows On, by Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 93)
- Publication--No Doubt About It, in the Cavlier. (Box 93)
- Reviews--Amazing Amazon. (Box 93)
- British American--legal papers. (Box 94)
- Clippings. (Box 94)
- Correspondence. (Box 94)
- Correspondence--Everybody's Magazine editorial office. (Box 94)
- Correspondence--Santos Dumont bio. (Box 94)
- Ephemera. (Box 94)
- Genealogy. (Box 94)
- Journal Entries--Rose Brown. (Box 94)
- Manuscript--Aleantara about Treasure. (Box 94)
- Manuscript--Buy British, by Bob Brown. (Box 94)
- Manuscript--Life of a Seringueiro. (Box 94)
- Manuscript--Midnight, by Rose Brown. (Box 94)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 94)
- Manuscript--The Careerist. (Box 94)
- Manuscript--When Chauncey Came. (Box 94)
- Serial Novel--Brambel Hill, by Robert Carlton Brown. (Box 94)
- Soviet Trip--Brochures and Advertisements. (Box 94)
- Clippings--Basic English: A Globalanguage. (Box 95)
- Clippings--Obituary, Rose Brown, Brazil Herald. (Box 95)
- Clippings--Reviews of "Look Before You Cook". (Box 95)
- Contract--Dances of our good neighbors. (Box 95)
- Correspondence. (Box 95)
- Correspondence--re: Argentina Gold Mine. (Box 95)
- Document--Entrevista com Rose e Robert Brown sobre a arte medieval Americana. (Box 95)
- Document--Project for establishing the Association of Inter-American Museums. (Box 95)
- Ephemera. (Box 95)
- Folio--Book Block of the Apocalypse. (Box 95)
- Gastronomy--Notebook. (Box 95)
- Gastronomy--Recipes. (Box 95)
- Manuscript--A Day on the Luziero, by Jessse Halliwell. (Box 95)
- Manuscript--A History of New York Newspapers. (Box 95)
- Manuscript--Amazon Folk Festivals. (Box 95)
- Manuscript--America Goes West. (Box 95)
- Manuscript--Iquitos, Peru. (Box 95)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 95)
- Manuscript--The Complete Book of Cheese. (Box 95)
- Manuscript--To Vote or Not to Vote. (Box 95)
- Manuscript--Traitors on Trial. (Box 95)
- Manuscript--Vote Bait. (Box 95)
- Notebook. (Box 95)
- Notes/Scrap Paper. (Box 95)
- Notes--Chapter list for "Good Neighbor Treasure Hunt," by Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 95)
- Notes--Memories of the Amazon. (Box 95)
- Clippings. (Box 96)
- Correspondence. (Box 96)
- Correspondence--letters from Bob to Rose after her death. (Box 96)
- Ephemera. (Box 96)
- List--Amazon Artifacts. (Box 96)
- Manuscript (incomplete). (Box 96)
- Manuscript/Notes--Sue's Zoo. (Box 96)
- Manuscript--on Russia. (Box 96)
- Manuscript--Reading the Smart Set in Buenes Aires, by Bob Brown. (Box 96)
- Memorandum of Association for British American. (Box 96)
- Notes/Scrap Paper. (Box 96)
- Notes--Ideas for Childrens Books, by Rose Brown. (Box 96)
- Clippings. (Box 97)
- Clippings--Announcement of British American. (Box 97)
- Clippings--Review of The New Caravan (anthology including Brown). (Box 97)
- Clippings--Reviews of Most for Your Money Cookbook, by Cora, Rose, and Bob Brown. (Box 97)
- Correspondence. (Box 97)
- Correspondence--re: Arthur Craven. (Box 97)
- Correspondence--re: Paul Bowles & Tangier. (Box 97)
- Correspondence--re: W.C. Williams, Book folder 3 of Paterson. (Box 97)
- Ephemera. (Box 97)
- Gastronomy--Recipes. (Box 97)
- Manuscript--A Bird in the Hand. (Box 97)
- Manuscript--A Fish Story. (Box 97)
- Manuscript--A Long-Shot at Longchamp. (Box 97)
- Manuscript--Amurica, I Love You. (Box 97)
- Manuscript--Anti-Nazi Quiz. (Box 97)
- Manuscript--Bible Leaf. (Box 97)
- Manuscript--Carnival No Rua. (Box 97)
- Manuscript--Close Finish. (Box 97)
- Manuscript--Father of a Million Plots. (Box 97)
- Manuscript--The Case of the Convent Girl. (Box 97)
- Manuscript--The Crime of Paraiba Street, by "John S. Brackett". (Box 97)
- Obituary Statements for Rose Brown. (Box 97)
- Pamphlet--Toward a Bloodless Revolution, by Bob Brown. (Box 97)
- Publication--Across the Corridor (serial novel). (Box 97)
- Publication--Giggle Butts, by Bob Brown. (Box 97)
- Publication--Keep Your Eye on the Ball, by Bob Brown. (Box 97)
- Rose Brown's Purse. (Box 97)
- Manuscript (incomplete). (Box 98)
- Manuscript--"Little Faust" and the Modern Amazon, by John S. Brackett. (Box 98)
- Manuscript/Notes--Let There Be Beer!. (Box 98)
- Manuscript--Gypsy's Revenge. (Box 98)
- Manuscript--Hochzeit With the German Cowboys, by Bob Brown. (Box 98)
- Manuscript--It Happened Aboard the "Matinee Boat". (Box 98)
- Manuscript--Lover Leaps and the Death Pact. (Box 98)
- Manuscript--My First Writing Friends. (Box 98)
- Manuscript--Old Dynamite. (Box 98)
- Manuscript--Ollie Wants a Cone. (Box 98)
- Manuscript--One Good Lick. (Box 98)
- Manuscript--Radio Lullaby in its Cradle. (Box 98)
- Manuscript--Rubles, Dollars, and Vodka. (Box 98)
- Manuscript--She Killed Him to Keep Him. (Box 98)
- Manuscript--Sir Isaac. (Box 98)
- Manuscript--Society Notes. (Box 98)
- Manuscript--The Inaugural Ceremonies. (Box 98)
- Manuscript--The Man and the Mango. (Box 98)
- Manuscript--The Red Skins of Munich. (Box 98)
- Notes/Scrap Paper. (Box 98)
- Notes--Autobiography (1886-1896). (Box 98)
- Notes--Detailed Bibliography. (Box 98)
- Notes--on Kay Boyle. (Box 98)
- Notes--on Rose and Bob before marriage (by Cora Brown?). (Box 98)
- Notes--on wine. (Box 98)
- Notes--Original and synopses filed at the Screen Writers Guild, by Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 98)
- Notes--Writing Friends of 50 Years. (Box 98)
- Poetry--untitled draft. (Box 98)
- Publication--Drug Store in a Dry Town, in American Mercury. (Box 98)
- Publication--Greenwich Village Gallops, in American Mercury. (Box 98)
- Publication--Pages from the Book of Beer, in American Mercury. (Box 98)
- Publication--The American Writer's Plight, in International Literature. (Box 98)
- Announcement--Roving Eye Press Selected Poems. (Box 99)
- Autobiographical Notes--Books and I are Bound. (Box 99)
- Bibliography. (Box 99)
- Carl Sandburg--Poem on Robert Carlton Brown. (Box 99)
- Clippings. (Box 99)
- Correspondence. (Box 99)
- Correspondence--to Carl Sandburg. (Box 99)
- Correspondence--to Kay Boyle. (Box 99)
- Cover Art--Three on a Raft, by Rose Brown. (Box 99)
- Drafts, Clippings, Notes, Correpsondence--Biography of Santos Dumont. (Box 99)
- Ephemera. (Box 99)
- Financial Papers--Sale of Petropolis Property. (Box 99)
- Gastronomy--Advertisement for Brown Cookbooks, with biographical statements. (Box 99)
- Gastronomy--Notes. (Box 99)
- Gastronomy--Recipes. (Box 99)
- Manuscript/Notes--Our Ears Should Burn, by Bob Brown. (Box 99)
- Manuscript--Father of a Million Plots. (Box 99)
- Manuscript--Fellow Countrymen Come to See Us. (Box 99)
- Manuscript--Gran Circo Buffalo Bill. (Box 99)
- Manuscript--I'm So Confused. (Box 99)
- Manuscript--My First Literary Friends. (Box 99)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 99)
- Manuscript--The Man and the Mango. (Box 99)
- Notes, Clippings, Drafts, Correspondence--Biography of Santos Dumont. (Box 99)
- Notes/Scrap Paper. (Box 99)
- Address book for Rio and Petropolis. (Box 100)
- Clippings. (Box 100)
- Correspondence. (Box 100)
- Correspondence--from Carlton Brown. (Box 100)
- Draft for Obituary of Bob Brown--unknown author. (Box 100)
- Ephemera. (Box 100)
- Map of Munich. (Box 100)
- Notes--"I married him to reduce him", Eleanor Brown. (Box 100)
- Notes/Scrap Paper. (Box 100)
- Notes--Bibliographic Information. (Box 100)
- Notes--Forty Years of Freelancing. (Box 100)
- Notes--On Rose's Will. (Box 100)
- Notes--Proposal for "The Burning Question" (book on smoking). (Box 100)
- Notes--Tables for the Complete Book of Cheese. (Box 100)
- Periodical--CONTEMPO III.ii. (Box 100)
- Poetry--"A Truly Friendly Capitalist". (Box 100)
- Poetry--"Mice and Men". (Box 100)
- Poetry--Drafts. (Box 100)
- Poetry--from "Amurica, I Love You". (Box 100)
- Poetry--published copy of "Amurica, I Love You". (Box 100)
- Publication--Fish, by Robert Carlton Brown. (Box 100)
- Publication--Letters of Gertrude Stein in Berkeley: A Journal of Modern Culture. (Box 100)
- Publication--The Sears-Roebuck Saga, by Bob Brown. (Box 100)
- Review of Globe Gliding by Ben Hagglund (in "The Rebel Poet"). (Box 100)
- Watercolor--dancing nude. (Box 100)
- Clippings. (Box 101)
- Correspondence. (Box 101)
- Ephemera. (Box 101)
- Gastronomy--Articles in Culinary Review, by Bob Brown. (Box 101)
- Gastronomy--Book proposal for Top of the Table Cooking, by Cora, Rose, and Bob Brown. (Box 101)
- Gastronomy--Miscellaneous Notes. (Box 101)
- Gastronomy--Notes, Clippings. (Box 101)
- Gastronomy--Recipes. (Box 101)
- Gastronomy--Reviews of Most For Your Money Cookbook, by Cora, Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 101)
- Manuscript--All Souls in Entrevaux, by Rose Brown. (Box 101)
- Manuscript--Alpine Symphony, by Rose Brown. (Box 101)
- Manuscript--At the French Salon, by Rose Brown. (Box 101)
- Manuscript--Easter Morn, by Rose Brown. (Box 101)
- Manuscript--Flaming Youth, by Bob Brown. (Box 101)
- Manuscript--From Balas to Balangandams, by Robert Carlton Brown. (Box 101)
- Manuscript--Herr Reflector, by Bob Brown. (Box 101)
- Manuscript--Living Dangerously, by Bob Brown. (Box 101)
- Manuscript--One Good Lick, by Bob Brown. (Box 101)
- Manuscript--Review of Wolfe Kaufman's "Tender Cheeks," by Rose Brown. (Box 101)
- Manuscript--Rough Diamond. (Box 101)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 101)
- Manuscript--The Dual, by Bob Brown. (Box 101)
- Manuscript--The Finger of God, by Rose Brown. (Box 101)
- Manuscript--The Rah-Rah Boys on the Rah-de-da, by Bob Brown. (Box 101)
- Manuscript--Triangle, by Rose Brown. (Box 101)
- Manuscript--Twisty Capello's Last Killing, by Rose Brown. (Box 101)
- Manuscript--Two Ghosts With One Stone, by Rose Brown. (Box 101)
- Manuscript--Wonder Where They Are?, by Bob Brown. (Box 101)
- Notes--Bob Brown's comments on editorial revisions of The Complete Book of Cheese (re: American Language). (Box 101)
- Notes--Daily entries on Bob's health by Rose Brown. (Box 101)
- Notes--List of stores about Tomba da Serra, by Rose Brown. (Box 101)
- Notes--Our Amazon Trip From Pacific to Atlantic. (Box 101)
- Notes--Outline for Autobiography. (Box 101)
- Notes--Table of Contents for "Brazil," travel book by Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 101)
- Manuscript--"Starving" Russia, by Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 102)
- Manuscript--A Provencal Elegy. (Box 102)
- Manuscript--Adventures of Hans Staden. (Box 102)
- Manuscript--Flower Flag Men. (Box 102)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 102)
- Manuscript--Star Dust on Our Shoulders, by Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 102)
- Manuscript--Traitors on Trial. (Box 102)
- Notebook. (Box 102)
- Notes/Scrap Paper. (Box 102)
- Notes--Amazon Artifacts. (Box 102)